caption by goraniworks Please note that the translation might not be perfect as it’s done by an AI(GPT4) model.
caption by goraniworks AI(GPT4)モデルによる翻訳なので、完全ではないかもしれないことにご注意ください。
Are you all enjoying the holiday?
皆さん、連休は楽しく過ごしていますか？
Hello, where am I? I'm on my way to the radio station.
こんにちは、私はどこかな？ラジオDJに向かっています
So, I decided to do a live broadcast after a long time.
だから久しぶりにライブを始めました
I was wondering if our Lovelinus are resting well during the holiday? Are you ready for the radio show?
私たちLovelynessのみんなは、連休をしっかり休んでる？ラジオの準備はできてるかなと思って
I turned on the live because it's been such a long time and I feel sorry about it.
こんな風に始めたけど、久しぶりにライブをするので申し訳ない気持ちもあります
I've kept it on.
ずっと続けています
You're all doing well, right?
みんな元気にしてる？
Let's do this.
うん、これでいいかな
Right now, Brother Seongjae is in Qatar, so
はい、今、성재オッパがカタールにいるので
I'm acting as the special DJ for the radio this week.
今週は私がラジオのスペシャルDJをしています
We have a live broadcast at 10 PM tonight.
皆さん、今夜10時に生放送があります
Where can you watch it?
どこで見られるんだろう？
EraoTV?
エラオTV？
Anyway, something on the internet.
とにかく、インターネットで
You can find out how to watch it by searching online, right?
インターネット検索すれば、どうやって見るかわかるでしょう？
Ah, you can watch it there too.
あ、そこでも見られるね
If you search "Bae Seongjae" on KakaoTV, you'll probably find it.
カカオTVで「배성재」を検索すれば、多分見られるはずです
Anyway, since it's a radio you can see,
とにかく、見えるラジオだから
if you have time, please watch the radio show as well.
時間が大丈夫な方は、是非ラジオも見てください
It's been a while since I've done a live,
はい、久しぶりにライブを始めると
seeing our Insta-friends after such a long time
久しぶりに見る私たちのインスタの友達
is really nice.
とても嬉しいです
Have you all gone to your hometowns?
皆さん、故郷に帰りましたか？
Lip? Uh, I'm not sure what that is.
リップ？あ、リップが何かわからない
I'm not sure what lip is, sorry.
リップが何かわからない、ごめんなさい
I'm not sure about the lip.
リップがわからない
Dinner is a banana.
夕食はバナナ
Because last night,
なぜなら、昨夜
So today, I'm going to make do with a banana.
今日はバナナで済ませます
"Unnie, you're going to have a fan meeting this year too, right?"
"お姉さん、今年もファンミーティングしますよね？"
I really want to do it too,
私も本当にやりたいから
so I'll try to make it happen.
できるようにちゃんと作ってみます
I can't promise,
確約はできないけど
Hold on, I'll peel a banana.
ちょっと待って、バナナを剥きます
But I thought it had warmed up a bit, but it's still a bit cold today.
でも、天気が暖かくなったと思ったら、今日もちょっと寒かったです
Peeling a banana.
バナナを剥く
Eating a banana like this
こんな風にバナナを食べて
and drinking milk,
牛乳を飲むと
makes it banana milk.
バナナミルク
"Finishing the day happily after seeing the live broadcast after work."
"仕事終わりに携帯を見たらライブしてて、とても幸せな一日の終わり"
Thank you, Haruka.
ありがとう、ハルカ
It's really been a while since I drank milk,
久しぶりに牛乳を飲むけど
and it tastes good after a long time, doesn't it?
久しぶりに飲むと
Milk is tasty?
牛乳が美味しいですね？
When I was young, I used to drink plain milk reluctantly.
子供の頃は白い牛乳を無理やり飲んでいたんです
As I grew up,
やはり成長すると
it seems my taste has changed.
味覚が変わるみたいです
There was plain milk for school meals when I was young, right?
子供の頃は白い牛乳の給食がありましたよね
When I was young, I drank it reluctantly and mixed it with all sorts of things,
子供の頃は無理やり飲んで、いろいろ混ぜて飲んだりしてたけど
but nowadays, I drink plain milk just fine.
最近は白い牛乳も普通に飲みます
Everyone,
皆さん
have you gone to your hometown?
故郷に帰りましたか？
I really enjoy watching ELLE Dong videos.
ELLE Dongの動画、とても楽しく見ています
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
I also enjoy watching my ELLE Dong videos.
私も私のELLE Dongの動画
"I can't go to my hometown, so I'll sleep watching the radio show."
"故郷に帰れないのでラジオを見て寝ようと思います"
Good idea.
いい考えです
I saw the WABAR video earlier, thank you.
さっきWABARの動画を見ました、ありがとうございます
I happened to connect with Brother Wadi like this,
私もワディオッパとこんなに繋がりができて
so we filmed together.
一緒に撮影しましたが
It was really fun.
とても楽しかったです
I'm not going to my hometown.
私は故郷には帰りません
I'm not going to my hometown,
私は故郷に帰らず
because I have things to do in Seoul.
ソウルでやるべきことがあるので
So, I think I'll be in Seoul.
ソウルにいると思います
But really, eating just one banana and milk together gives a lot of satiety.
でも、本当にバナナ一本と牛乳を一緒に食べると少し
It feels very filling.
とても満腹感があるような気がします
My stomach is too full.
お腹がとてもいっぱいで
My stomach is really full.
お腹がとてもいっぱいです
The one I just ate is the second one.
さっき食べたのが二本目です
I ate one at home earlier,
さっき家で一本食べて
and I thought I might get hungry again,
何かまたお腹が空くかもしれないから
so I ate another one in the car.
車でまた一本食べて
Ah, so I was at Tokoya, I left my hat again,
あ、だからトコヤ、私がいるんだけど、また帽子を忘れてきちゃって
please take good care of that hat for me.
その帽子、ちゃんと預かっておいてください
I always leave something behind.
いつも何かしら忘れていくね
Anyway, that's how it is.
とにかくそんな感じ
Please watch, everyone. Today is the last day.
皆さん、見てください。今日が最後です
But the things we've pre-recorded will go out on the radio on Saturday and Sunday,
行くところは、でも今録音したものが
and they're already up on YouTube,
土曜日と日曜日にラジオで放送されます
so everything that's been prepared will be available.
YouTubeにはもう録音してあるので
Today is already the last day, but the radio has been
すべて用意してあります
What are you all doing during the holiday?
とても面白いです
What are your plans for the holiday?
私は連休に何をして休もうかな、皆さん
Have you all gone to your hometown?
皆さんの連休の計画は何ですか？
Maybe everyone has gone to their hometown.
皆さん、故郷に帰ったのかな
Drinking milk with red vinegar, I know what that is.
牛乳と紅酢を一緒に飲むの、私、何かわかります
It becomes somewhat like yogurt, right?
それで、ちょっとヨーグルトみたいになるんですよね
What's on sale at Costco these days for 120,000 won?
最近コストコでセールして、何が12万ウォンで売ってるの？
But I've arrived at the radio, everyone.
でも、私、ラジオに到着しました、皆さん
Why can't you go to your hometown?
なぜ故郷に帰れないの？
During the holiday, it's whiskey.
連休はウィスキーですよね
Right, whiskey is good, but after finishing work during the holiday,
そう、ウィスキーもいいけど、連休に何か仕事終わりに
I feel like drinking wine.
ワインが飲みたくなりそうで
Before coming to the radio show,
さっきラジオに来る前に
I bought three bottles of wine from a local wine shop.
近所のワインショップでワインを3本も買いました
Two bottles of white wine,
白ワイン2本と
and one bottle of red wine.
赤ワインを一本買ったんですけど
One of the white wines is a recent favorite of mine,
白ワインは最近好きな白ワインと
and the other is said to be very similar to that wine but a few ten-thousands of won cheaper.
それととても似ているけど、もう少し安いワインがあるって
So, I was curious about that and bought a bottle of it too.
だからそれも気になって、それも一本買いました
And I really like Caymus wine,
そして、私はカイマスワインがとても好きなんですけど
but if you buy it in Korea, it's currently selling for about 140,000 won.
そのワインを韓国で買うと、今、約14万ウォンで売ってるんですよ
But a bottle for 140,000 won isn't exactly cheap, right?
でも一本14万ウォンだと、実際安いワインではないですよね
There are more expensive wines, of course,
それよりもっと高いワインもたくさんありますが
but I got some recommendations for wines similar to Caymus,
だから、カイマスワインと似ているワインを少し勧められて
and thought about trying a different kind of wine, maybe an American wine since
カイマスとはちょっと違う感じのアメリカのワインを試してみたらどうかと
Because Caymus is an American wine.
だから、他のアメリカのワインも...
So, other American wines...
あっ、いや、いや、いや
Ah! No, no, no.
フランスのワイン...違う？
French wine... No?
どこだっけ？
Where was it?
どこだっけ？ガヨン？
Ah, where was it? Some...
あ、どこだっけ？なんの...
That wine is really famous in France,
そのワインがフランスでとても有名で
the only one to win 1st place in a blind test.
唯一ブラインドテストで1位になったワインって言ってたけど
Which country was it from?
どこの国のものだっけ？
What country was it?
どこの国だっけ？
Anyway, that's what they say, so
とにかく、そういうことらしいので
that...
その...
Not Caymus,
カイマス以外に
I also bought another red wine I'm trying for the first time.
初めて試す赤ワインも一本買いました
But Caymus is a bit sweet,
でもカイマスも少し甘いんですよ
it doesn't show up as having a lot of sugar content when you look it up, but
調べてみると、糖度がそれほど多いとは出てこないけど
it tastes sweet to me.
私が食べると甘いんです
But it's somewhat sweet and
でもその程度で少し甘くて
as rich as Caymus, they said there's another wine like that,
でもカイマスほどとても濃厚な
so I bought a bottle to try it.
別のワインだって言うから
That's why I bought three bottles,
それを試してみたくて
and it came out to just over 100,000 won.
一本買いました
Was it 140,000 won?
だからそうして三本買ったんですが
One bottle of Caymus is 140,000 won,
10万ウォン台前半でした
but today, in thrifty shopping, I got three bottles for 140,000 won.
14万ウォンだっけ？
Gotcha!
そのカイマス一本が14万ウォンで
Ah, continuously putting on a filter on my hand...
あ、フィルターをかけてずっと手に...
This red appearance looks a bit funny.
これ、赤い色がついたのちょっと面白いね
my skin is a bit troubled right now,
私、今、肌が少し荒れていて
I first turned it on with the normal quality...
最初に普通の画質で始めたんだけど...
I tried like this,
こんな風にやってみたら
but things like this on my forehead, like my skin troubles, are too visible,
あまりにもこの額のこれがよく見えるから
so today I thought I should push my skin a bit,
今日は肌を少し隠さないとと思って
That's it. It's been a while since I put on a filter...
全部やりました。久しぶりにフィルターを...
Anyway, I've arrived, so I have to go, everyone.
とにかく、私は到着したので行かないと、皆さん
If you want to see me again, please move to the radio show.
もう一度私を見たいならラジオに移動してください
It starts at 10 PM.
10時から始まります
Everyone,
皆さん
Goodbye, see you again.
さようなら、またね
Bye.
バイバイ